A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006
Library of Virginia
- III. Legislative Files, 2002-2005 (accession 42414)., Extent: 47.95 cubic feet (137 boxes). (Box 38-174)
  - 2005 Session
    - House of Delegates
      - HB 2007 (05) Transient Occupancy Tax; Imposition in Carroll County (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - HB 2010 (05) Judgment; Rate of Interest (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - HB 2012 (05) War Veterans Memorials includes Operation Iraqi Freedom (Box 148, Folder 1)
      - HB 2013 (05) Heritage Music Trail: The Crooked Road; Designating as Certain Highways in Southwest Virginia (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2018 (05) Bedding and Used Upholstered Furniture; Regulations (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2019 (05) Special License Plates; Prohibits Issuance unless certain Requirements Met (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2020 (05) Highway Repairs; Use of Steel Plates (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2022 (05) Motor Vehicle Dealers; Sale and Distribution of Fire-Fighting Equipment, Ambulances and Funeral Vehicles (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2027 (05) Economic Development; Services Provided to Economically Distressed Areas (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2029 (05) Nonindigenous Aquatic Nuisance Species; Prohibited without Permit, Penalty (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2031 (05) Dams; Authorizing Localities to Map Inundation Zones for those Areas that might be threatened (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2032 (05) Powers and Duties of Department of Emergency Management; FOIA (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2033 (05) Semi-Conductor Manufacturing Performance Grants; Updates to make Quality Manufacturer Eligible (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2036 (05) Long-Term Care; to Ensure Coordinated, Effective, and Efficient Services to Older Adults (Box 148, Folder 2)
      - HB 2037 (05) Interagency Civil Admissions Advisory Council; Created (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - HB 2038 (05) Midwifery; Licensure (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - HB 2041 (05) Neighborhood Assistance Act; Extends Tax Credits (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - HB 2047 (05) Higher Educational Institutions Bond Act of 2005; Created (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - HB 2049 (05) Virginia Capital Trail; Designating Portion of Route 5 between City of Richmond and Jamestown (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - HB 2050 (05) Unemployment Compensation; Weekly Benefit Amount (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - HB 2051 (05) Public Procurement Act; Purchase of Technology, etc. to be Approved by Chief Information Officer of State (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - HB 2052 (05) Clerks of Court; Prohibits Posting Personal Information on Internet (Box 148, Folder 3)
      - HB 2053 (05) Underground Utility Damage Prevention; Requires Notification of Abandoned Lines (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2054 (05) Alternative, Pilot Project; VITA to Study (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2055 (05) Telephone Privacy Protection Act; Prohibiting Telephone Solicitation, Date Change Made Consistent with Federal Regulation (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2059 (05) Credit Cards; Unlawful Use of Scanning Devices and Re-Encoders, Penalty (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2060 (05) Firearms; Exempts Law-Enforcement Officers from Limit of Purchasing One per 30-Day Period (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2061 (05) Economic Development Revolving Fund; Abolished (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2063 (05) County Manager Plan; Adds Items for which Arlington County may Charge Application Processing Fee (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2067 (05) Chesapeake Bay Bridge and Tunnel Commission; Provisions for Members (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2068 (05) Law-Enforcement Officers of Marine Resources Commission; Free Use of Certain Toll Facilities (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2071 (05) Southside Virginia Higher Education Center; Created (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2072 (05) Charter; Town of Halifax (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2073 (05) Sewage Sludge; Individual May Request Testing, Responsibility of Cost (Box 148, Folder 4)
      - HB 2078 (05) Antiquities Act; Creation of Position of State Archaeologist, Penalty (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2079 (05) Historic Preservation and Museum Assistance Grant Program and Fund; Created (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2080 (05) Historic Preservation; Appropriation of State Funds therefore (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2084 (05) Highway Construction, Maintenance and Improvement Commission, to let all VDOT Contracts (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2085 (05) Conservation Officers; Expands Jurisdiction and Allows Mutual Aid Agreements (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2086 (05) Conservation Officers; Change of Powers (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2094 (05) Judgment; Courts to Exercise Personal Jurisdiction over Officials from other States (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2098 (05) Child-Day Centers; Person Convicted of One Misdemeanor Offense may be Hired if 10 years have lapsed (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2100 (05) Retail Sales and Use Tax; Exemptions include Certain Nonprofit Entities (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2101 (05) Polling Places; Voter Required to Remain in Presence of Officers of Election until Vote Cast (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2102 (05) Blaze Orange Clothing; Exempts Person Hunting with Bow and Arrow in Areas where Firearms Prohibited (Box 148, Folder 5)
      - HB 2109 (05) Name Change; Service of Application for Minor Made on Parent who does not join in (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2110 (05) Involuntary Mental Commitment Hearing; Judge must apply Standard of Proof (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2111 (05) Conflict of Interest Act, State and Local Government; Disclosure of Economic Interests (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2112 (05) Lobbyists; Provision of Statements to Legislative and Executive Officials (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2114 (05) Detention Center Incarceration Program; Shall not be in addition to an Active Sentence (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2118 (05) Blood Alcohol Tests in Civil Cases; Admissibility of Written Results (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2120 (05) Escheat Grants; Requires Clerk to Accept for Recordation a Copy (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2123 (05) Dept. of Professional and Occupation Regulation; Unlicensed Activity (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2130 (05) Law-Enforcement Officers; Certain Allowed to Purchase Service Handgun (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2131 (05) General Assembly; Increase Session Per Diem of Administrative Assistants (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2136 (05) Conflict of Interests Act; Disclosure Filings (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2137 (05) Unemployment Tax Rate; Penalties for Transferring Any Trade or Business for a Lower Tax Rate (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2143 (05) Accident and Sickness Insurance; Insurer Required to Provide Notice of Premium Increase (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2144 (05) Gubernatorial Appointments; Confirmation Process (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2145 (05) Port Authority; Service Charge Payments to Localities (Box 149, Folder 1)
      - HB 2151 (05) Public Procurement Act; Preference for Contractor Firms (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2155 (05) Indigenous Wild Birds and Animals, Legally Taken; Allows Licensed Auctioneers to Sell Parts (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2156 (05) Speed Limits; May Be Set on Non-surface Treated Highways in Montgomery County (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2158 (05) Wireless Service Authority; Allows Multiple Localities and Regional Industrial Facilities to Create (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2159 (05) Boards of Zoning Appeals; Changes in Provisions (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2162 (05) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Holdover Tenancies with Landlord's Consent (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2163 (05) Child Abuse or Neglect; Child Protective Services to Investigate Complaint Against School Personnel (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2164 (05) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Termination of Rental Agreement for Fire or Casualty Damage (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2165 (05) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Noncompliance with Rental Agreement (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2166 (05) Long-Term Health Care; HHR Secretary to Develop Public Information Campaign (Box 149, Folder 2)
      - HB 2168 (05) Garbage; Trash, or Refuse Collection; Additional Requirements for Localities (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - HB 2169 (05) Charter; City of Winchester (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - HB 2170 (05) Commissioners of Accounts; Authorized to Establish Fee for Services (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - HB 2174 (05) Criminal Cases; Testimony of Husband and Wife (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - HB 2176 (05) Charter; Town of Stanley (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - HB 2177 (05) Recordation Tax; Exemptions include Limited Liability Companies (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - HB 2186 (05) Motor Vehicle Safety Inspection Approval Stickers; Allows Extension for Military Personnel (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - HB 2187 (05) Special License Plates; Increases Fee for Certain Officials and Constitutional Officers (Box 149, Folder 3)
      - HB 2189 (05) Motor Vehicle Registration; Requires Permanent Registration for Buses (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2192 (05) Landfill; Distance from Ground Water Supply and Required Replacement of Non-tidal Wetlands (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2193 (05) Driver's Licenses; Reduction in Number of Written Tests Given for Renewal (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2197 (05) Sewage Sludge; Notification to Local Government before Application to Land (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2198 (05) Sewage Sludge; Program Established to Train Employees for Testing thereof (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2199 (05) Motorcycles; Safety Inspection (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2200 (05) Crossbows; License for Hunting during Special Archery Seasons, Restricted Fee (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2206 (05) Juveniles; Change in Disposition for a Delinquent (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2209 (05) General District Court; Medical Records (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2210 (05) Charter; City of Waynesboro (Box 149, Folder 4)
      - HB 2212 (05) Natural Area Preservation Fund; Addition of Fees, Lease Proceeds, and Funds Accrued from Preserves (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2213 (05) Prisoners; Illegal to Possess Cellular Telephone, Penalty (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2215 (05) Computer Crimes Act; Changes in Provisions, Penalty (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2216 (05) Department of Forensic Science, the Forensic Science Board, Scientific Advisory Board; Created (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2217 (05) Gangs; Punishment for Activity Taking Place in School, etc., Penalty (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2218 (05) Gift Certificate Disclosures; Definition, Penalty (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2219 (05) Insurance; Insurer May Cap Renewal Rates for Certain Policies (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2221 (05) Animal Laws; Enforcement in Towns (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2223 (05) Student Expulsion; Procedures for Readmission (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2228 (05) Non-Conventional Sewage Disposal System; Schedule of Civil Penalties for Violation for Operation, etc. (Box 149, Folder 5)
      - HB 2234 (05) Hospital Authorities; Commissioners (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2236 (05) Patient Records; Protection of Health Data by Hospitals (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2237 (05) Practitioner of Self-Referral Act; Exemption (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2238 (05) Emergency Medical Services Personnel Training, Response Times, etc., Civil Penalties (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2242 (05) Pharmacy Interns; Provisions (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2243 (05) Medical Care Facilities Certificate of Public Need; Parties to the Case (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2245 (05) Mental Health Services Transition Plan; Board of Juvenile Justice to Promulgate Regulations (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2247 (05) Sexual Assault; Crime when Committed on Physically Helpless Person of Any Age (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2248 (05) Sexual Crimes Against Spouses; Changes in Provisions (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2249 (05) Motorists; Prohibits certain Activities on Highways in Albemarle and Greene Counties (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - HB 2253 (05) Emergency Medical Services Plan, Statewide; New Requirements, and Deletion of Cross References (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2255 (05) Alcoholic Beverages; Underage Drinking, Possession of, etc., Penalty (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2260 (05) Advertising Signage; Certain Historic Buildings Not Currently Operating as a Pharmacy to Display (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2266 (05) Character Education; Harassment Prevention Required (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2267 (05) Harassment; Immunity for any School Employee, Student, etc., who Reports Incident (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2268 (05) Food Stamps; Eligibility for Transitional Benefits (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2273 (05) Hunting; Prohibits Device/Service that Remote Controls Firearms, etc., to Hunt Birds, etc., Penalty (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2275 (05) Warning Lights; Use of Red and White Lights by Department of Environmental Quality (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2277 (05) Oversize Vehicles; Use of Cameras in Identification (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2278 (05) Oversize Vehicles; Driving into or through Tunnels, Penalty (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - HB 2282 (05) Sport Shooting Ranges; Certain Specified Criteria for Localities (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2283 (05) Public Procurement Act; Provision of Default Contract Claim Procedure (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2284 (05) Family Access to Medical Insurance Security Plan; Changes in Benefits (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2286 (05) Extended Service Contract; Increases Fee for Registering or Renewing Registration (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2287 (05) Jurors; those Serving in Courts of Record (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2288 (05) Criminal Investigation; Obstruction of Justice, Penalty (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2291 (05) Controlled Substances; Raises Penalty for Manufacturing, Selling, etc. (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2293 (05) Motor Vehicle Titles; Allows Creation of Electronic Certificates of Title (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2295 (05) Farmers; Certain Exempt from Dairy Regulations for Goat Cheese Products (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2298 (05) Mennel Milling Company; Conveyance of Land in Roanoke County (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2301 (05) Criminal History Record Information; Allows Free Check for Council of Girl Scouts (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - HB 2303 (05) State Income Tax; Voluntary Refund Contributions Entities Process Changes (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2305 (05) Indigent Defense Commission; Regulation for Appointment of Chairman (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2310 (05) Mechanic's Lien; Increases Limits for Repairs and Storage for Keeper of Stable, Garage, Marina, etc. (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2315 (05) Bonds; Change in Length of Time Defendant has to Appear in Court, Forfeiture for Failure to Appear (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2316 (05) Nursing Home Bed Projects; Conditions for Issuance of an Amended Certificate of Public Need (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2318 (05) Juveniles; Judicial Discretion to Require Registration of Minor who Commits Registrable Offense (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2321 (05) Reporting Requirements of Certain Agencies and Collegial Bodies (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2325 (05) State Income Tax; Extension for Filing Tax Returns (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2326 (05) Sheltered Workshops; Requires Division of Purchases and Supply to Adopt Regulations to Support (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2336 (05) William H. Hume and Jean Emmons McCarty Hume Memorial Bridge; Designating Portion of Route 688 (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - HB 2337 (05) Articulation Agreements; Admission of Community College Students into Four-Year Public Institution (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2338 (05) Companion Animals; Requirement of Permit to Sell, Penalty (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2341 (05) Claims; H. Steven Arrington, Carolyn Dixon, Betty Earle and E. Anthony Ware (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2342 (05) Special License Plates; Issuance to Law-Enforcement Chaplains (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2363 (05) Health Records; Emphasizes Right of an Individual to have Access thereto, Exceptions (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2364 (05) Planning District Commissions; Membership (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2365 (05) Storm Water Management Program; Updates for Department of Conservation and Recreation Authorities (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2366 (05) Hospitals and Nursing Homes; Board of Health must include Minimum Standards for Design and Construction (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2367 (05) Fees; Waiver for Filing Erroneous Financing Statements (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2368 (05) Dentists and Dental Hygienists; Licensure and Continuing Education (Box 150, Folder 5)
      - HB 2369 (05) Prisoners; Individual Court Orders Permitting Work Not Required (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2371 (05) Unemployment Compensation; Disqualifications for Chronic Absenteeism (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2372 (05) Business License Tax, Local; Population Basis and Fee Increases (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2376 (05) Elected Officials; Terms of Office, and Authorization of Members of Board to Administer Oath (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2377 (05) Inoperable Motor Vehicles; Conforms Civil Penalty Provisions for Violations of Ordinances (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2378 (05) Wetlands Board, Local; Members that Hear Cases Relating to Chesapeake Bay Preservation Ordinance to Serve on (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2379 (05) Emergency Management; Allows Local Director to Enter into Mutual Aid Arrangements (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2381 (05) Community Development Authorities; Removes Population and Tract Size Limits for Counties (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2382 (05) School Division Residency; False Statements, Penalty (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2383 (05) Electoral Board Members and General Registrar Staff; Costs of Defense shall be Paid by State (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2384 (05) Commissioner of Accounts; No Requirement when Beneficiary is Trustee (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2386 (05) Conveyance of Easements; Eliminates Public Hearing Requirement for Localities (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2391 (05) Grass; Isle of Wight County given authority to Require Property Owners to Cut (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - HB 2393 (05) Employee's Day of Rest; Abolished (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2399 (05) FOIA; Exempts Certain 911 or E-911 Records (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2400 (05) Heritage Music Trail: The Crooked Road; Designating as Certain Highways in Southwest Virginia (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2404 (05) FOIA; Exempts Certain Local Wireless Service Authorities (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2406 (05) Charter; Town of Coeburn (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2407 (05) Comprehensive Plans; Includes Provisions for Elderly and Persons with Disabilities (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2408 (05) Sewage Disposal Fees; Included on Real Estate Tax Bills (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2410 (05) Medical Malpractice Insurance; Cancellation or Non-Renewal Notice of Policy (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2411 (05) State Income Tax; System of Taxation and Conformity with Internal Revenue Service Code (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2412 (05) Voter Registration Drive; Increases Penalty for Destruction of, Failure to Mail or Deliver Application (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2415 (05) Provisional Ballots; Written Notice of Meeting of Electoral Board to be given to Voter (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - HB 2416 (05) Unemployment Compensation; Changes in Provisions (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2418 (05) Speed Limits; Definition of in Residence and Business Districts (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2420 (05) Latino Advisory Board; Created (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2422 (05) Southwest Virginia Higher Education Center; Membership (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2423 (05) Horse Industry Board Act; Created, Penalty (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2427 (05) Wetlands; Prohibits Condemnation of Any Property for Compensatory Mitigation (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2428 (05) Veterans; State in Hiring to give Additional Consideration to Certain (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2429 (05) Prescription Monitoring Program; Includes Reporting by Out-of-State Dispensers (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2430 (05) Health Care Services; Safety and Quality by Physicians (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2431 (05) Practitioners; Information Provided to Patients (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2433 (05) Domestic Violence and Prevention Services; Responsibilities of Department (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2434 (05) Motor Vehicle Safety Inspection Stations; Garage Liability Insurance (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - HB 2435 (05) Motor Vehicles; Notice of Impoundment (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2436 (05) Prisoners; Continued Hospitalization of those Involuntarily Admitted (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2438 (05) Methamphetamine; Manufacturing when Person under 18 Years of Age is Present, Penalty (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2440 (05) Hazardous Waste Facilities; Financial Assurances therefore (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2444 (05) State Income Tax; Extends Sunset Provision for Tax Credit Rent Reductions (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2446 (05) Condominium and Property Owners' Association Acts; Charges for Disclosure Packets (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2447 (05) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Drug Activities by Tenants, Forfeiture (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2448 (05) Landlord and Tenant; Installation of New Lock or Security Device after Entry of Certain Court Orders (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2449 (05) Manufactured Home Park; Termination of Tenancy (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2450 (05) Storm Water; Regulation of Billing Charges (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2451 (05) Septic Systems; Validity of Septic Tank Permits (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - HB 2452 (05) Non-Native Oysters; Marine Resources Commission to Allow Placement on State-Owned Bottomlands (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - HB 2454 (05) Charitable Gaming; Registration of Bingo Callers, Payment of Remuneration (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - HB 2455 (05) Baseball Stadium Authority; Entitlement to Tax Revenues (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - HB 2456 (05) Zoning Ordinances; Cash Proffers Requested or Accepted by a Locality (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - HB 2457 (05) Money Transmission Services; Exemption from Licensure (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - HB 2459 (05) State Income Tax; Credit for Restoration of a Historic Presidential Home (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - HB 2460 (05) Credit Counseling; Eliminates Requirement that Licensed Agencies be Non-Profit and Tax-Exempt (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - HB 2461 (05) Residential Facilities; Board who Regulates to Provide Name, etc. of Contact Person (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - HB 2462 (05) Worker's Compensation; Certain Participants in Temporary Assistance for Needy Families Not Eligible (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - HB 2464 (05) Stream Channel Restoration and Relocation Projects; Exempt Certain from Requirements (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - HB 2470 (05) Uniform Electronic Transactions Act; to include Locally Elected Constitutional Officers (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - HB 2471 (05) Computer Crimes Act; Changes in Provisions, Penalty (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - HB 2475 (05) Charter, Town of Lovettsville (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - HB 2477 (05) Machinery and Tools Tax; Changes in Valuation Method Published by Notice in Newspaper 30 Days Prior (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - HB 2478 (05) Contracts; Eliminates Cap on Percentage of Payment Errors Contractor May Retain for Recovery Audit (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - HB 2482 (05) Personal Information Privacy Act; Restricting Use of Social Security Numbers (Box 152, Folder 1)